Guide to the Joseph Albertson films,circa 1960-1970
Albertson, Joseph films, 1960-1970.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joseph Albertson films, circa 1960-1970
7308
Joseph Albertson
29 films
Videotapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Films by Albertson and others with primarily male homosexual and some heterosexual erotic themes.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Films by Albertson and others with primarily male homosexual and some heterosexual erotic themes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Albertson, Joseph.
Subjects:
Homosexuality.; Gay men.
Form and Genre Terms:
Erotica.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Male Undress, Pose Beach Frolics, Nude in Boat, Gone with the River, Five Nude Surfers, early 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- The Take Off, The Pick Up, The Blue Rose, early 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Nudist Desert Safari, Camping Out, early 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Lake Como, Florida, 1971; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Zoro, Fire Island, N.Y., 1970; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Mr. Hercules, Billy Hill and Friend, Patio Antics, Poser at Pool, Aztec Sacrifice, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Psychomontage, Love Making, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Two Faces of Sex, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Gay Europe, 1966; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Doctor's Office, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Minitaurus, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Five Nudes in Pool, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Three Way and Duo, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Rover Boys, Part 1, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Rover Boys, Part 2, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Posing Movies, (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Kangaroo Court, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Roxanne and Photographer, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Anatomy of Tom, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Bryan and Kevin, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Nude Men Exercise, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Male Nudist Keeps Fit #1, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Lazy Sailor, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Amateur Photographer, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Dial M for Men, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- The Posing Strap, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Sal., 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- The Friendly Couple, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)
- Beechwood, PA two samples, 1960s; (8mm film) (Box 1)